{
    "subject": "resource/Lucian_Freud",
    "predicate": "property/deathDate",
    "object": "2011-07-20",
    "human_readable": "Lucian Freud died on July 20, 2011.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8552737832069397,
            "question": "When did Lucian Freud die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5412747859954834,
            "question": "What year was Lucian Freud born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5348944067955017,
            "question": "Where was Lucian Freud from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4033629298210144,
            "question": "Was Lucian Freud a painter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2607251703739166,
            "question": "How did Lucian Freud influence the art world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2529536485671997,
            "question": "Did Lucian Freud have any famous relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22862236201763153,
            "question": "What is Lucian Freud known for in art history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2108684778213501,
            "question": "Who are some of Lucian Freud's most famous subjects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17799288034439087,
            "question": "How would you describe the style of Lucian Freud's paintings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1638333946466446,
            "question": "What are some recurring themes in Lucian Freud's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lucian Freud died on July 20, 2011.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3994_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the style of Lucian Freud's paintings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3994_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Lucian Freud's most famous subjects?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3994_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Lucian Freud known for in art history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3994_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3994_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the multiple documents provided which all mention that Lucian Freud died on July 20, 2011. Each file contains this information in one form or another, supporting the statement \"Lucian Freud died on July 20, 2011.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}